Hi, my name is Jeremy Lee,
and this is my project,
an intelligent sleeve called CLYF.
For climbers, we don't really know:
how long should we be resting?
So I made this intelligent sleeve
that tracks your muscle signals
and your muscle pressure
in your forearm.
As you can see,
there's a battery here.
When you start climbing or gripping,
you can see the battery decreasing.
After a few seconds, say you get very tired,
you could come down off the wall.
You just hands off, and you can see
that the battery is charging back.
After it gets to a certain baseline
designed for your body—
say it's like 80 here.
Let's just wait.
Okay, now it's going,
so you should be climbing again.
Okay, that's it. Thank you.